// You can specify the question limit
const QUESTION_LIMIT = 400;

// Limit for timer
const TIMER_LIMIT = 20;

// Select the colors of choices in a string
const CHOICE_COLOR = "teal";

// You can add new questions and answers in following JSON format:
// {question: "blabla", answer:"foo"}


const QUESTIONS_ANSWERS = [
    {question:"Abolish",answer:"Feshetmek"},
    {question:"Accustom", answer:"Alıştırmak"},
    {question:"Acknowledge",answer:"Onaylamak"},
    {question:"Acquire",answer:"Edinmek"},
    {question:"Allocation",answer:"Tahsis"},
    {question:"Allowence",answer:"Harçlık"},
    {question:"Amend",answer:"Düzeltmek"},
    {question:"Ample",answer:"Bol"},
    {question:"Anchor",answer:"Çapa"},
    {question:"Attendant",answer:"Refakatçi"},
    {question:"Auction",answer:"Açık Arttırma"},
    {question:"Bale",answer:"Balya"},
    {question:"Banal",answer:"Sıradan"},
    {question:"Baneful",answer:"Zararlı"},
    {question:"Banish",answer:"Sürgün etmek"},
    {question:"Basin",answer:"Havza/Leğen"},
    {question:"Bawl",answer:"Haykırarak ağlamak"},
    {question:"Bladder",answer:"Mesane"},
    {question:"Blister",answer:"Kabarcık"},
    {question:"Bolt",answer:"Cıvata/Somun"},
    {question:"Bony",answer:"Kemikli"},
    {question:"Bribe",answer:"Rüşvet"},
    {question:"Briefcase",answer:"Evrak çantası"},
    {question:"Brooch",answer:"Broş/İğne"},
    {question:"Brow",answer:"Alın"},
    {question:"Carryover",answer:"Nakletmek"},
    {question:"Cash register",answer:"Yazarkasa"},
    {question:"Caterpillar",answer:"Tırtıl"},
    {question:"Cauliflower",answer:"Karnabahar"},
    {question:"Cease",answer:"Durdurmak/Kesmek"},
    {question:"Chamber",answer:"Oda"},
    {question:"Charter",answer:"Kiralama/Araç Rezervasyonu"},
    {question:"Cheeky",answer:"Küstah/Kaba"},
    {question:"Chilly",answer:"Soğuk"},
    {question:"Chimney",answer:"Baca"},
    {question:"Chuckle",answer:"Kıkırdama"},
    {question:"Clutch",answer:"Debriyaj/Kavrama"},
    {question:"Colonel",answer:"Albay"},
    {question:"Comet",answer:"Kuyruklu Yıldız"},
    {question:"Commemorate",answer:"Anmak (saygıyla)"},
    {question:"Commute",answer:"İşe gidip gelmek"},
    {question:"Compansate",answer:"Karşılamak (zararı)"},
    {question:"Compromise",answer:"Uzlaşma (Taviz vererek)"},
    {question:"Condemn",answer:"Kınamak/Mahkum etmek"},
    {question:"Conduct",answer:"Yönetmek"},
    {question:"Consent",answer:"Rıza/Razı olmak"},
    {question:"Consequently",answer:"Sonuç olarak"},
    {question:"Consign",answer:"Sevk etmek/Teslim Etmek"},
    {question:"Constitute",answer:"Kurmak"},
    {question:"Constitution",answer:"Anayasa"},
    {question:"Convict",answer:"Suçlu/Mahkum"},
    {question:"Cope",answer:"Başa çıkmak"},
    {question:"Cordon",answer:"Polis kordonu"},
    {question:"Cork",answer:"Mantar"},
    {question:"Crane",answer:"Vinç"},
    {question:"Crude",answer:"Ham"},
    {question:"Cushion",answer:"Minder"},
    {question:"Debt",answer:"Borç"},
    {question:"Decay",answer:"Çürümek"},
    {question:"Defer",answer:"Ertelemek"},
    {question:"Deliberately",answer:"Kasten"},
    {question:"Deputy",answer:"Milletvekili"},
    {question:"Dew",answer:"Çiy"},
    {question:"Digest",answer:"Sindirmek"},
    {question:"Dim",answer:"Sönük"},
    {question:"Dip",answer:"Daldırmak"},
    {question:"Directory",answer:"Dizin/Rehber"},
    {question:"Disclose",answer:"Açığa çıkarmak"},
    {question:"Distinct",answer:"Belirgin/Farklı"},
    {question:"Dismay",answer:"Dehşet"},
    {question:"Dispatch",answer:"Sevk etmek"},
    {question:"Doom",answer:"Kötü Kader"},
    {question:"Doomsday",answer:"Kıyamet"},
    {question:"Down payment",answer:"Peşinat"},
    {question:"Draft",answer:"Taslak"},
    {question:"Drain",answer:"Boşaltmak/Lağım"},
    {question:"Draught",answer:"Taslak/Hava akımı"},
    {question:"Eel",answer:"Yılan Balığı"},
    {question:"Embark",answer:"Gemiye/Uçağa binmek"},
    {question:"Embrace",answer:"Kucaklamak"},
    {question:"Emphasize",answer:"Vurgulamak"},
    {question:"Entitle",answer:"Hak Vermek/Başlık vermek"},
    {question:"Epitaph",answer:"Kitabe/Mezar yazıtı"},
    {question:"Evacuate",answer:"Tahliye etmek"},
    {question:"Exclaim",answer:"Haykırmak"},
    {question:"Extinguish",answer:"Söndürmek"},
    {question:"Fed up",answer:"Bıkmak"},
    {question:"Fertile",answer:"Gübre"},
    {question:"Fig",answer:"İncir"},
    {question:"Fiscal",answer:"Mali"},
    {question:"Flea",answer:"Pire"},
    {question:"Flee",answer:"Kaçmak"},
    {question:"Foreman",answer:"Ustabaşı"},
    {question:"Forge",answer:"Demir dövmek"},
    {question:"Forger",answer:"Sahtekar/Kalpazan"},
    {question:"Forthwith",answer:"Derhal"},
    {question:"Fragile",answer:"Kırılgan"},
    {question:"Frontier",answer:"Ülke hududu"},
    {question:"Fuse",answer:"Sigorta"},
    {question:"Fuss",answer:"Yaygara/Telaş"},
    {question:"Germ",answer:"Mikrop"},
    {question:"Ginger",answer:"Zencefil"},
    {question:"Grumble",answer:"Homurdanma/Söylenme"},
    {question:"Gulf",answer:"Körfez"},
    {question:"Handicap",answer:"Engel"},
    {question:"Head-quarters",answer:"Karargah/Merkez"},
    {question:"Hinge",answer:"Menteşe"},
    {question:"Hose",answer:"Hortum"},
    {question:"Hubbub",answer:"Şamata"},
    {question:"Impair",answer:"Bozmak/Zarar vermek"},
    {question:"Incentive",answer:"Teşvik edici"},
    {question:"Incident",answer:"Olay"},
    {question:"Incidentally",answer:"Bu arada/Tesadüfen"},
    {question:"Indefinite",answer:"Belirsiz"},
    {question:"Indemnity",answer:"Tazminat"},
    {question:"Indorse",answer:"Ciro"},
    {question:"Inflammable",answer:"Yanıcı"},
    {question:"Inflate",answer:"Şişmek"},
    {question:"Insolvent",answer:"Müflis"},
    {question:"Insulate",answer:"Yalıtmak/İzole etmek"},
    {question:"Intangible",answer:"Manevi"},
    {question:"Interfere",answer:"Müdahale etmek"},
    {question:"Intestines",answer:"Bağırsaklar"},
    {question:"Invoice",answer:"Fatura"},
    {question:"Jack",answer:"Kriko/Priz/Vale"},
    {question:"Jackal",answer:"Çakal"},
    {question:"Knob",answer:"Tokmak"},
    {question:"Ladle",answer:"Yemek kepçesi"},
    {question:"Lash",answer:"Kamçı"},
    {question:"Lease",answer:"Kiralamak (Gayrimenkulü)"},
    {question:"Liquidate",answer:"Şirketi kapatmak (Tasfiye)"},
    {question:"Loan",answer:"Ödünç vermek/Borç"},
    {question:"Lorry",answer:"Kamyon"},
    {question:"Margin",answer:"Kenar boşluğu"},
    {question:"Mattress",answer:"Yatak/Şilte"},
    {question:"Meadow",answer:"Çayır"},
    {question:"Merely",answer:"Sadece/Ancak"},
    {question:"Merit",answer:"Liyakatli/Değmek"},
    {question:"Mild",answer:"Ilımlı/Hafif"},
    {question:"Millet",answer:"Darı"},
    {question:"Miser",answer:"Cimri"},
    {question:"Mislay",answer:"Yanlış yere koymak/Kaybetmek"},
    {question:"Mole",answer:"Köstebek"},
    {question:"Moss",answer:"Yosun"},
    {question:"Murmur",answer:"Mırıltı"},
    {question:"Mutter",answer:"Fısıltı"},
    {question:"Notorious",answer:"Adı çıkmış/Kötü şöhretli"},
    {question:"Oar",answer:"Kürek/Kürekçi"},
    {question:"Oasis",answer:"Vaha"},
    {question:"Oblige",answer:"Mecbur etmek/Zorunda bırakmak"},
    {question:"Omit",answer:"Atlamak/Hariç Tutmak"},
    {question:"Orchard",answer:"Meyve bahçesi"},
    {question:"Overtime",answer:"Fazla mesai"},
    {question:"Oyster",answer:"İstridye"},
    {question:"Parade",answer:"Geçit töreni"},
    {question:"Pastime",answer:"Eğlence/Hoş zaman"},
    {question:"Pea",answer:"Bezelye"},
    {question:"Pearl",answer:"İnci"},
    {question:"Penknife",answer:"Çakı"},
    {question:"Pension",answer:"Emeklilik/Pansiyon"},
    {question:"Peril",answer:"Tehlike"},
    {question:"Picket",answer:"Kazık/Gözcü"},
    {question:"Pincers",answer:"Kerpeten"},
    {question:"Pioneer",answer:"Öncü"},
    {question:"Plum",answer:"Erik"},
    {question:"Porter",answer:"Kapıcı/Hamal"},
    {question:"Power of attorney",answer:"Temsil yetkisi"},
    {question:"Power house",answer:"Elektrik Santralı"},
    {question:"Privilage",answer:"Ayrıcalık/İmtiyaz"},
    {question:"Propeller",answer:"Pervane"},
    {question:"Proportion",answer:"Orantı"},
    {question:"Prosecute",answer:"Dava açmak"},
    {question:"Proverb",answer:"Atasözü"},
    {question:"Publicity",answer:"Tanıtım/Tanıtma"},
    {question:"Pull up",answer:"Sağa çek"},
    {question:"Quota",answer:"Kota"},
    {question:"Railing",answer:"Korkuluk/Parmaklık"},
    {question:"Ram",answer:"Koç/Toslamak"},
    {question:"Rash",answer:"Aceleci/İsilik"},
    {question:"Recession",answer:"Ekonomik durgunluk"},
    {question:"Recollect",answer:"Hatırlamak"},
    {question:"Reconcile",answer:"Arabuluculuk etmek"},
    {question:"Refreshment",answer:"Ferahlatcı/Hafif yiyecek-içecek"},
    {question:"Regulation",answer:"Yönetmelik"},
    {question:"Reluctant",answer:"İsteksiz"},
    {question:"Remedy",answer:"Çare(Hastalığa)"},
    {question:"Remit",answer:"Havale/Affetmek"},
    {question:"Resent",answer:"İçerlemek/Alınmak"},
    {question:"Reside",answer:"İkamet etmek"},
    {question:"Retail",answer:"Perakende"},
    {question:"Retaliation",answer:"Misilleme/öç"},
    {question:"Revenue",answer:"Gelir"},
    {question:"Rug",answer:"Kilim"},
    {question:"Rust",answer:"Pas"},
    {question:"Sandpaper",answer:"Zımpara kağıdı"},
    {question:"Saucer",answer:"Fincan Tabağı"},
    {question:"Savour",answer:"Tadını çıkarmak/Lezzet"},
    {question:"Scone",answer:"Çörek"},
    {question:"Scroff",answer:"Ense"},
    {question:"See over",answer:"Gözden geçirmek/Kontrol etmek"},
    {question:"Serviette",answer:"Peçete"},
    {question:"Shortage",answer:"Kıtlık"},
    {question:"Shrink",answer:"Çekmek/Küçülmek"},
    {question:"Skim",answer:"Sıyırmak (köpüğü)"},
    {question:"Smuggle",answer:"Kaçakçılık"},
    {question:"Snag",answer:"Engel/Budak"},
    {question:"Snub",answer:"Terslemek/Kalkık uçlu"},
    {question:"Solidarity",answer:"Dayanışma"},
    {question:"Spanner",answer:"İngiliz anahtarı"},
    {question:"Stall",answer:"Ahır/Oyalamak"},
    {question:"Stapler",answer:"Zımba"},
    {question:"Stationary",answer:"Kırtasiye"},
    {question:"Steep",answer:"Sarp/Dik"},
    {question:"Steward",answer:"Kahya"},
    {question:"Stool",answer:"Tabure/Dışkı"},
    {question:"Strain",answer:"Zorlanma, Gerginlik"},
    {question:"Strainer",answer:"Süzgeç"},
    {question:"Strap",answer:"Kayış"},
    {question:"Stretcher",answer:"Sedye"},
    {question:"Stutter",answer:"Kekemelik/Kekelemek"},
    {question:"Subsidize",answer:"Mali yardım yapmak"},
    {question:"Summit",answer:"Dağ Zirvesi/Zirve(toplantı)"},
    {question:"Suppress",answer:"Baskılamak"},
    {question:"Swan",answer:"Kuğu"},
    {question:"Swollen",answer:"Şişkin/Şişmiş"},
    {question:"Tan",answer:"Bronzlaşmak"},
    {question:"Tangerine",answer:"Mandalina"},
    {question:"Tangible",answer:"Maddi/Somut"},
    {question:"Tape-measure",answer:"Mezura"},
    {question:"Tariff",answer:"Tarife"},
    {question:"Tempt",answer:"Baştan çıkarmak"},
    {question:"Tenant",answer:"Kiracı"},
    {question:"Thorough",answer:"Kapsamlı/Eksiksiz"},
    {question:"Tide",answer:"Gelgit"},
    {question:"Tuition",answer:"Öğrenim"},
    {question:"Tummy",answer:"Karın/Mide"},
    {question:"Turnkey",answer:"Anahtar teslimi"},
    {question:"Turnover",answer:"Devir"},
    {question:"Typist",answer:"Daktilo/Daktiloda yazan kişi"},
    {question:"Undergo",answer:"Geçirmek (ameliyat)"},
    {question:"Urban",answer:"Kentsel/Şehir"},
    {question:"Vaporize",answer:"Buharlaşmak"},
    {question:"Veil",answer:"Duvak/Peçe"},
    {question:"Velvet",answer:"Kadife"},
    {question:"Venture",answer:"Riskli Girişim"},
    {question:"Verdict",answer:"Karar/Hüküm"},
    {question:"Viable",answer:"Geçerli"},
    {question:"Vice",answer:"Mengene/Kötülük"},
    {question:"Vicious circle",answer:"Kısır döngü"},
    {question:"Vulture",answer:"Akbaba"},
    {question:"Wager",answer:"Bahis"},
    {question:"Waistcoat",answer:"Yelek"},
    {question:"Warder",answer:"Gardiyan/Bekçi"},
    {question:"Ware",answer:"Eşya"},
    {question:"What's more",answer:"Dahası"},
    {question:"Whim",answer:"Heves/Kapris"},
    {question:"Windscreen",answer:"Ön cam (araç)"},
    {question:"Windpipe",answer:"Soluk Borusu"},
];

const QUESTIONS_ANSWERS_SET_2 = [
    {question:"dedication", answer:"özveri"},
    {question:"insight", answer:"içgörü/kavrama"},
    {question:"tendency", answer:"eğilim"},
    {question:"fulfilling", answer:"tatmin edici"},
    {question:"ensure", answer:"sağlamak"},
    {question:"foster", answer:"gayretlendirmek"},
    {question:"jeopardize", answer:"tehlikeye atmak"},
    {question:"exploit", answer:"faydalanmak"},
    {question:"profound", answer:"engin/derin"},
    {question:"impartial", answer:"tarafsız"},
    {question:"instil", answer:"aşılamak"},
    {question:"contagious", answer:"bulaşıcı"},
    {question:"poultry", answer:"kümes hayvanları"},
    {question:"turmoil", answer:"kargaşa"},
    {question:"dispute", answer:"anlaşmazlık"},
    {question:"docile", answer:"uysal"},
    {question:"bystander", answer:"seyirci"},
    {question:"plummet", answer:"düşmek"},
    {question:"paltry", answer:"değersiz"},
    {question:"peculiarly", answer:"bilhassa/garip bir şekilde"},
    {question:"subsequent", answer:"sonraki"},
    {question:"infant", answer:"bebek"},
    {question:"unprecedented", answer:"benzeri görülmemiş"},
    {question:"potent", answer:"güçlü"},
    {question:"elicit", answer:"meydana çıkarmak"},
    {question:"maritime", answer:"denizcilik"},
    {question:"jurisdiction", answer:"yargı yetkisi"},
    {question:"clarification", answer:"açıklama"},
    {question:"deterioration", answer:"bozulma"},
    {question:"migration", answer:"göç"},
    {question:"confine", answer:"sınırlamak"},
    {question:"overtly", answer:"açıkça/sır olmayan"},
    {question:"cognitive", answer:"bilişsel"},
    {question:"eventually", answer:"sonunda"},
    {question:"fluctuate", answer:"dalgalanmak"},
    {question:"limb", answer:"uzuv"},
    {question:"favour", answer:"olumlu bakmak"},
    {question:"enhance", answer:"genişletmek"},
    {question:"prospect", answer:"olasılık"},
    {question:"immense", answer:"engin/muazzam"},
    {question:"courteous", answer:"nazik"},
    {question:"convey", answer:"iletmek"},
    {question:"nourish", answer:"beslemek"},
    {question:"shrine", answer:"türbe/tapınak"},
    {question:"abandonment", answer:"terk etme"},
    {question:"lethal", answer:"öldürücü"},
    {question:"conventional", answer:"geleneksel"},
    {question:"relieve", answer:"rahatlama"},
    {question:"adorn", answer:"süslemek"},
    {question:"endure", answer:"katlanmak"},
    {question:"eredicate", answer:"kökünü kurutmak"},
    {question:"rousing", answer:"heyecan verici"},
    {question:"vibrant", answer:"canlı"},
    {question:"prejudice", answer:"ön yargı"},
    {question:"drawback", answer:"dezavantaj"},
    {question:"inquiry", answer:"soruşturma"},
    {question:"transmission", answer:"bulaşma"},
    {question:"delicate", answer:"narin"},
    {question:"vigorous", answer:"güçlü"},
    {question:"excessive", answer:"aşırı"},
    {question:"elaborate", answer:"ayrıntılı"},
    {question:"swift", answer:"süratli"},
    {question:"drastically", answer:"şiddetle"},
    {question:"hinder", answer:"engellemek"},
    {question:"encompass", answer:"kapsamak"},
    {question:"burden", answer:"sorumluluk"},
    {question:"counterpart", answer:"karşılık"},
    {question:"accommodate", answer:"uyum sağlamak"},
    {question:"vague", answer:"belirsiz"},
    {question:"manuscript", answer:"el yazması"},
    {question:"foremost", answer:"önde gelen"},
    {question:"adverse", answer:"ters/olumsuz"},
    {question:"residue", answer:"kalıntı"},
    {question:"compound", answer:"bileşik"},
    {question:"colossal", answer:"devasa"},
    {question:"diverse", answer:"çeşitli"},
    {question:"misery", answer:"sefalet"},
    {question:"scoff", answer:"alay etmek"},
    {question:"upheaval", answer:"ayaklanma"},
    {question:"tenet", answer:"ilke"},
    {question:"memoir", answer:"hatıra"},
    {question:"tailored", answer:"uyarlanmış"},
    {question:"intrusion", answer:"ihlal/zorla girme"},
    {question:"scholar", answer:"akademisyen"},
    {question:"overwhelming", answer:"ezici/bunaltıcı"},
    {question:"firmly", answer:"sıkıca"},
    {question:"indispensable", answer:"vazgeçilmez"},
    {question:"inconclusive", answer:"sonuçsuz"},
    {question:"unprecedented", answer:"benzeri görülmemiş"},
    {question:"eligibly", answer:"uygun şekilde"},
    {question:"adequate", answer:"yeterli"},
    {question:"stem from", answer:"kaynaklanmak"},
    {question:"ingenuity", answer:"yaratıcılık"},
    {question:"indigenous", answer:"yerli"},
    {question:"pest", answer:"haşere"},
    {question:"prompt", answer:"yönlendirmek"},
    {question:"oppress", answer:"ezmek"},
    {question:"neglect", answer:"ihmal"},
    {question:"deter", answer:"caydırılmak"},
    {question:"deceiver", answer:"hilekar/aldatıcı"},
    {question:"venom", answer:"zehir"},
    {question:"expose", answer:"maruz kalma"},
    {question:"innately", answer:"doğuştan"},
    {question:"predispose", answer:"yatkınlık"},
    {question:"resemble", answer:"benzemek"},
    {question:"adherence", answer:"bağlılık"},
    {question:"prevalence", answer:"yaygınlık"},
    {question:"detrimental", answer:"zararlı"},
    {question:"relieve", answer:"azaltmak"},
    {question:"attain", answer:"ulaşmak"},
    {question:"endow", answer:"bağışlamak"},
    {question:"dispell", answer:"kovmak"},
    {question:"adolescence", answer:"gençlik"},
    {question:"assurance", answer:"güvence"},
    {question:"evident", answer:"belirgin"},
    {question:"mediocre", answer:"vasat"},
    {question:"strictly", answer:"kesinlikle"},
    {question:"manifest", answer:"belirgin/göstermek"},
    {question:"retain", answer:"sürdürmek"},
    {question:"contamine", answer:"kirletmek"},
];

const QUESTIONS_ANSWERS_PREP_CONJ = [
    {question:"upon", answer:"üzerine"},
    {question:"over", answer:"üzerinde"},
    {question:"as though", answer:"sanki"},
    {question:"by means of", answer:"aracılığıyla"},
    {question:"along", answer:"boyunca"},
    {question:"whereas", answer:"oysa/böyle olduğu halde"},
    {question:"yet", answer:"ancak"},
    {question:"ought to", answer:"yapmalı"},
    {question:"with regard to", answer:"bakımından"},
    {question:"nonetheless", answer:"yine de/her şeye rağmen"},
    {question:"alongside", answer:"yanında"},
    {question:"namely", answer:"yani"},
    {question:"seldom", answer:"nadiren"},
    {question:"provided that", answer:"şartıyla"},
    {question:"along with", answer:"birlikte"}
];

const QUESTIONS_ANSWERS_PHRASALS = [
    {question:"take up", answer:"işe başlamak"},
    {question:"call for", answer:"çağrıda bulunmak"},
    {question:"pass over", answer:"görmezden gelmek"},
    {question:"give in", answer:"teslim olmak/etmek"},
    {question:"in spite of", answer:"rağmen"},
    {question:"do away with", answer:"yok etmek"},
    {question:"cut down on", answer:"kısmak"},
    {question:"bring about", answer:"neden olmak"},
    {question:"come down with", answer:"nedeniyle hastalanmak"},
];

export {QUESTIONS_ANSWERS, QUESTION_LIMIT, TIMER_LIMIT, CHOICE_COLOR, QUESTIONS_ANSWERS_SET_2, QUESTIONS_ANSWERS_PREP_CONJ, QUESTIONS_ANSWERS_PHRASALS};

/*
    {question:"", answer:""},
    {question:"", answer:""},
    {question:"", answer:""},
    {question:"", answer:""},
    {question:"", answer:""},
*/